Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One Piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place that
the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary till
someone proves it real.
Through it all, through
all the trouble and times.
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along.
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything.
That we're looking for.
There's always room for you.
If you wanna be my friend.
We are, we are on a cruise.
We are.
What's wrong with you, Zoro?
You look like you're having a
really bad day or something.
I've already demonstrated my way of the
Six Blades to these pathetic humans,
and there's no way you can hope
to defeat me in that condition.
Oh, just shut up already.
Big Bro, he's taken such a beating.
Unsure the onset of fever caused by his
wounds is making him delirious, or worse.
If that wound opens up again,
I'm afraid he'll die for certain.
But he doesn't have time to
think about that right now.
Yeah, and he's the only one who
can fight that six-sword freak.
I'll show you.
Three-sword style.
Yosaku, Johnny, lend me your swords.
Of course.
Big bro, catch! Damn it.
I'm losing it.
I don't know how much longer I can last.
Big bro, here they come!
Catch them!
Ha!
Now you'll understand why two human
hands never have a chance to beat me!
Six blades!
Watch out!
Tentacle sword overload!
Big road!
Three sword style!
Streaming wolf swords!
He did it!
He faced all six swords,
and not even a scratch!
Perfect sword skill, with
perfect concentration!
How dare you cut me like that!
Now I'm really mad!
I'll kill you, bastard!
There's no way you'll
survive my next attack.
You just got lucky is all.
You'll never beat my six
swords with your three.
I have twice as many swords as you.
Don't you get it?
Six is more.
I was never very good at math.
What is it then?
What weight do you
carry on your shoulders?
Three swords.
Six swords.
Does it matter?
You may have more swords than me, but mine
will always carry more weight than yours.
He's only been drowned for a little while.
If we can get him back
up, we can revive him.
Damn it.
I can't swing hard enough
underwater to break this thing.
Hurry, Conis.
It's no use.
I can't break it.
He needs oxygen now, but there's
no time to get an air canister.
And we can't carry him up with this rock.
That's it!
Weight, you say?
It may not look like it, but my
swords actually weigh quite a bit.
Over 300 pounds each, to be exact.
They weigh much more than
your pathetic human swords.
I meant the burden of... Oh, forget it.
Weigh of six swords!
Octopus pot stands!
New Year's!
Open!
Body slam!
Shame shot, stupid octopus! How's that?
Big bro! He's dead!
You'll never touch the ground alive!
Waltz of six swords!
You'll be mid-speed if you
touch debris for even a second!
Big bro!
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Yeah!
Ah!
All right!
Damn it!
First you timed your roll to
dodge my tentacle sword overload!
Then you slice and dice my hands
up like some cheap sushi chef!
How dare you make a spectacle
of my master swordsmanship!
You'll pay for that, you son of a bitch!
I'll tear you limb from limb look at that.
He's in pain
That attack it probably
opened up his wounds again.
Yeah, I wish I could
take his place right now
Even if this wound
would kill a normal man?
Not allowed to fail!
Way of six swords octopus pot
stands time to die sorrow.
I cannot feel the pain.
Must not.
New Year's!
If I'm ever going to face Hawkeye as
an equal, I must be extraordinary!
Dragon Twister!
Archie, defeated,
three-sword style.
So,
Fish, now you finally understand the
weight I carry in my three swords.
You satisfied?
All right, now the
tentacles is out of the way.
I think it's time to go rescue Luffy.
Look out!
How could you do that to Hoxie?
You!
You thought you'd gotten rid of me, huh?
Not bad.
I didn't know there was
anyone in all of the East
Blue who could stand back up
after one of my punches. Oh, sure.
There's a whole bunch.
At a certain restaurant
I know of. Wanna go?
I don't think so.
Big Crow, don't do it!
What do you think you're doing?
You're dead if you go
in the water like that.
Just shut up.
It won't last much more.
You think you ladies might
want to stop chatting?
Yeah.
Time's up.
If I could get you to
shut up for a moment,
maybe you would have noticed
that I was about to do this.
Here goes nothing!
That's great!
He wants to try his luck in the water!
Against the fish man! Stupid!
But I told you, they want
us to fight in the water!
That man is from Cocoyashi Village.
They've stretched out Luffy's neck.
I'm sorry, but this is
the best I can do for you.
please try to breathe
please come back damn it I
can't hold my breath much
longer you have to come
back now I see I couldn't
move the stone so they
just moved Luffy's head
above the water all I have to
do is break the rock apart
in the situation should
take care of itself
this
is more like somebody else
do something entertaining
it's that old man from
the village what a waste
of time damn it he sees me
such a pathetic attempt
trying to keep rubber
boy alive i guess i'll just kill you too
where do you think you're
going you foolish human
are you really trying to fight me underwater
you can't even breathe down here what
makes you think you can fight as you wish
foolish boy fishman
karate dueling hair cover
too bad your kick is powerless down here
that's more of your human weakness but my
fish man karate loses nothing in water
quite the contrary it's much more powerful
fish man karate underwater ladder buster
Bishman Karate!
Flaming Axe Kick!
Backfoot Jawbreaker!
Cafe!
Bamba!
Air, air, air!
I let out too much!
I can't breathe!
Suffocating!
Impressive.
Crap, let me through.
I need to breathe.
Move it.
You have amazing stamina.
You sure you're human?
Let me through now.
Didn't you say something like, any man
who hurts a lady is just a piece of crap?
And yet, look at what your precious
love of women has finally gotten you.
you have no escape and you'll die by
my hand the old man and the boy he's
trying to save they'll die too i'll
kill zoro and the long-nosed guy then
i'll massacre the entire village and
as my final pleasure i'll murder that
traitorous bitch nami don't you see your
love is worthless If it can't save you,
then you protect no one!
Not even your little girlfriend, Nami!
I'll admit that you have some skills.
But still, in the end,
you're just a human.
Your body doesn't react well to a
sudden change in pressure, does it?
Let's see.
I have a theory about what's
going to happen to you.
Your organs are going to
explode from the inside out.
Pulverizing pressure plowers!
I can't let him do this.
If I want to save Nami, the first
thing I have to do is save myself.
What's with him?
He just won't die.
Very well.
I guess we'll just have to try it again.
Fishmen use their lungs
to breathe air on land,
but they use their gills
to breathe water down here.
Which means a fish's gills
are useless on dry land.
Ready for your second Grand?
And their lungs are useless underwater.
Which means forcing air into his
gills should suffocate this bastard!
You don't worry he's okay are you sure?
Yeah half of him wait
half I'll explain later.
First get your ass up here I want
to fight where I can breathe!
You still don't get it do you?
It doesn't matter to me if
I'm on land or in the water.
I'm just as strong either way now you will
witness the true power of fishman karate.
When I punched you before that was
just a sample of things to come!
My ultimate attack is
ten times as powerful
and the chances you'll
survive it are zero.
Your neck!
You said my love was worthless?
Shoulder!
I can't protect anyone, is that right?
Rips! Back! Chest!
Legs!
Son of a bitch!
Thousand brick vests!
And now, face shot!
Now it's done.
He won't be back.
Caribou?
Hachi?
In the end, they're all just seafood.
A fish can't fight a cook.
I don't know what he was thinking.
This game is ours.
You bastards.
You've killed my brothers
one after the other.
I'm afraid I've let you
get too carried away.
All right, explain.
Luffy's half-okay?
What does that mean?
It means he's alive for the time being.
But if we want him fully back on dry
land, I've got to go back in the water.
But something tells me ugly
over there won't let me.
Amazing.
Really amazing.
Those guys beat two of
Arlong's best fishmen.
I'm done.
I can't hold my breath.
Take my place. I'll go.
You spit out a bunch of water.
Did I miss anything?
They're doing great.
Everyone's fine.
For the first time.
I think I have hope.
These guys have fought so well.
We may actually be set free.
Chew, what a pain in the ass.
That long-nosed freak
sure could run forever
But it took just one blast from my
squirt gun to take him out completely
I guess I should head back
It's all over by now for sure
It worked, I'm alive I'm so glad I made
the ketchup star for such occasions
He thinks he killed me with a
water blast Run along now, go home
these guys are totally freaking nuts
i don't even know what i'm doing here
they destroyed an entire
village and killed everyone in
it i know nami can't do this
all on her own but seriously
i'm hearing things i don't mind hiding
from death death is scary let's see i'm
covered in fake blood but i need to look a
little more beat up like i fought bravely
hey i know what's
missing dirt yeah huh too
clean hey i'm sorry i
got lost yeah that's good
no i did my best but he got me maybe i was
this close to the bastard
and he got away Hey,
that sounds better.
Nah, it sounds like I'm trying too hard.
We're friends, right? So get on!
How about...
Don't cry, Nami.
We all did the very best we could.
Never in my life did I imagine it lose.
Or...
Everybody fought very bravely.
But the truth is that our idiot captain is
far better than a gang
who'd prey on a lady.
Maybe...
I nearly died myself.
It's for my business.
This was my only choice.
Nami, no.
To tell the truth, my
injuries aren't bad at all.
Really.
Big Sis Nami was crying.
Do they need any more reason than
that to put their lives on the line?
To make a choice like
that when you're only ten.
Do you know how hard that
must have been for Nami?
I fought bravely.
I never quit.
Yeah, that's...
I'm just...
a liar!
I'm nothing but a coward!
Stop right there, you son of a bitch!
Oh?
You're still alive, Chu.
That's right, big lips!
It takes more than water
to kill someone like me!
Chu.
When I left home, I
left everything behind.
Peace.
Safety.
When you live your life on the edge
you savor every moment that's why
they're able to laugh so much that's
the reason I went to sea I want to laugh
that way too if I don't fight with
all I got then I don't deserve to be
on the same ship with them and I'll
never be able to face my friends again?
Fool, you were better off
pretending to be dead.
The human brain is an
absolute waste of meat.
I don't feel good.
Oh yeah?
I'm just getting started.
Stop it!
Usopp hammer! Yeah!
Usopp rubber band of doom!
Chew?
Ah, crap!
Where did that stupid son of a bitch go?
I can't believe this.
Special attack.
Saki? Let's go.
Is this the only way you
can fight, you coward?
There is no place to hide
from my squirt cannon.
Stupid coward or whatever,
I can't run from this fight.
I'm supposed to be a man,
although it doesn't really feel
all that great to be manly.
If I lose, I'll die.
At least I'll die a pirate.
Squirt cannon!
Damn it, why should I have to
waste my time with such an idiot?
It's too easy.
I'll shred you to pieces.
Squirt machine gun!
How did he find me?
Crap, crap, holy crap!
I wanted to be a real pirate, and
now that I've finally got my chance!
I know I can do it! I
know I can! I promise!
If I survive this ordeal, I'll never
pretend to be a pirate ever again!
I won't be a coward and run away!
My fake pirate days are over!
What did you say is done?
This whole fight!
Alcohol lights on fire!
Usopp, flaming star!
Fire!
Hot!
Water! Must find water! Water!
Wait a minute! Water! Water!
What's that?! Hammer!
Shoot!
AAAAAAAH!
BASTARD!
Usopp Hammer!
I did it.
I beat a fish man.
You see that loser?
I beat your ass.
I can't believe I actually did it.
Who's a pirate now?
I am Usa the Pirate!
Watch the sunrise,
I began to wonder What could be
the reason it's so hot inside?
No answer has come, but I can't
get away from what's true.
It's because of you!
Show me how to catch those feelings,
get them to come back to me?
I'll do what I must be, cause
they're everything I want to be.
Pass these arms around my dreams
and pull them back from yesterday.
If I'm holding hands with you,
I'm sure that we can make the way.